Yash Nihalani

Pune, Maharashtra / M.No: 7987523930/7028462350 / Email: ynihalani08@gmail.com

PGDM in Marketing and Finance with four years of experience in retail banking for loans and sales marketing. Experienced in business loans, CIBIL observation, obligations cross verification with CIBIL and banking, inward return, outward return, ITR analysis, profit and loss account, balance sheet observation, business premise visit, observation of business, drafting PD report and send it to credit manager for finalization. Customer Service, Investments, Outbound calling, Operations and Fraud Prevention while working across multiple roles in driving business by managing product, platform & distribution network.

Skills:

- Marketing of products, customer service
- Analyzing business profile, login process of disbursement, analysis of 3 years financial statement, ITR, balance sheet, profit and loss accounts
- Physical visit at business premise, observing business setup, activity, stock, employees to ensure compliance.
- BTL and promotional activities for retail and wholesale relationship programs

Experience:

NOVEMBER 2023 - JUNE 2024

AU Small Finance Bank, Pune / Relationship Officer

- 1. Opening salary accounts of several Enterprise Companies like IT Companies, Manufacturing, FMCG and Pharmaceutical companies. It also includes schools, colleges, hospital and restaurants.
- 2. On boarding new enterprise companies with Au small finance while engaging in B2B activities via cold calling, linkedin, just dial, fundoo data and india mart platform. Also conducting BTL activities like canopy in MSME Corporates and Showrooms of Maruti Suzuki and Honda.
- 3. Cross selling of Mutual Funds and Insurance products while opening various corporate clients accounts to strengthen revenue of the company.
- 4. Maintaining strong relationship with various branches of Au Small Finance Bank to get references for future business growth

JULY 2022 - JULY 2023

Mahindra Holidays & Resorts, Pune / Sales Executive

- 1. Selling holiday membership plans to a wide range of audience to make their every moment magical while holidaying with Club Mahindra luxurious resorts
- 2. Conducting BTL activities trade like direct mail campaigns, trade shows, brand promotion activities, canopies to attract corporate crowd, telemarketing and exhibitions to gather maximum number of prospects for generating maximum revenue
- 3. Giving presentations including resort videos, brochure briefing, stating the Resort USP's to the prospects whole family members while addressing their doubts and queries and also building relationship with them for future references.

JANUARY 2019 – JULY 2022

SBI Global Factors Limited, Pune / Assistant Manager

- 1. Generating business from CAT A and A+ builders along with strengthening relationship with them.
- 2. Providing excellent customer service to maintain long term relationship with developers
- 3. Successfully establish the good teamwork and ensure have a happy workplace
- 4. Verify documents to ensure proper documentation for internal and external auditors' review
- 5. Regular follow-ups with credit team and operations on timely basis to conduct business revenue
- 6. Handling HNI clients worth more than 10 crores while maintain strong relationships with corporates. Moreover converted more than 400 HNI clients during my tenure.
- 7. Convincing more and more customers to invest in fixed deposit and other third party products like demat, insurance and gold loans.

APRIL 2017 – OCTOBER 2018

Marketing Executive / Oppo Mobiles Private Limited, Pune

- Increasing business from retail and wholesale relationship programs.
- Conduct BTL activities and sales promotional activities in the region.
- Organize sales promotions and demos.

Internship Project / Godrej and Boyce, Pune

• Established contacts and develop relationships with prospects & achievement sales.

Scanned with CamScanner

• Finding the needs of customers for the Godrej Vending Machines in the following

markets, o Schools o Colleges o Multiplexes

Education:

JUNE - 2016

Post Graduate Diploma in Management / BITM, Pune Completed Post Graduate Diploma in Management in Finance and Marketing from Balaji Institute of Telecom and Management, Pune

JUNE - 2013

Bachelor of Business Administration/ SSIT, Ratlam Completed Bachelor of Business Administration from Shri Sai Institute of Technology, Ratlam

MARCH - 2010 12th / SGTBPHSS, Ratlam

Completed 12th on 2010 from Shri Guru Tegh Bahadur Public H.S School.

MARCH - 2008 10th / SGTBPHSS, Ratlam

Completed 10th on 2008 from Shri Guru Tegh Bahadur Public H.S School.